{
    "addition": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "problem": "$1 + 10$",
        "answer": 11
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "problem": "$12 + 4$",
        "answer": 16
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "problem": "$1 + 8$",
        "answer": 9
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "problem": "$8 + 3$",
        "answer": 11
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "problem": "$16 + 10$",
        "answer": 26
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "problem": "$15 + 9$",
        "answer": 24
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "problem": "$8 + 10$",
        "answer": 18
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "problem": "$13 + 9$",
        "answer": 22
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "problem": "$20 + 15$",
        "answer": 35
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "problem": "$20 + 10$",
        "answer": 30
      }
    ],
    "integrals": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "problem": "\\int{{4{x^6} - 2{x^3} + 7x - 4\\,dx}}",
            "answer": "{{\\frac{4}{7}{x^7} - \\frac{1}{2}{x^4} + \\frac{7}{2}{x^2} - 4x + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "problem": "\\int{{{z^7} - 48{z^{11}} - 5{z^{16}}\\,dz}}",
            "answer": "{{\\frac{1}{8}{z^8} - 4{z^{12}} - \\frac{5}{{17}}{z^{17}} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "problem": "\\int{{10{t^{ - 3}} + 12{t^{ - 9}} + 4{t^3}\\,dt}}",
            "answer": "{{ - 5{t^{ - 2}} - \\frac{3}{2}{t^{ - 8}} + {t^4} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "problem": "\\int{{{w^{ - 2}} + 10{w^{ - 5}} - 8\\,dw}}",
            "answer": "{{ - {w^{ - 1}} - \\frac{5}{2}{w^{ - 4}} - 8w + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "problem": "\\int{{12\\,dy}}",
            "answer": "{{12y + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "problem": "\\int{{\\sqrt[3]{w} + 10\\,\\,\\sqrt[5]{{{w^3}}}\\,dw}}",
            "answer": "{{\\frac{3}{4}{w^{\\,\\frac{4}{3}}} + \\frac{{25}}{4}{w^{\\,\\frac{8}{5}}} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "problem": "\\int{{\\sqrt {{x^7}} - 7\\,\\sqrt[6]{{{x^5}}} + 17\\,\\,\\sqrt[3]{{{x^{10}}}}\\,dx}}",
            "answer": "{{\\frac{2}{9}{x^{\\frac{9}{2}}} - \\frac{{42}}{{11}}{x^{\\frac{{11}}{6}}} + \\frac{{51}}{{13}}{x^{\\frac{{13}}{3}}} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "problem": "\\int{{\\frac{4}{{{x^2}}} + 2 - \\frac{1}{{8{x^3}}}\\,dx}}",
            "answer": "{{ - 4{x^{ - 1}} + 2x + \\frac{1}{{16}}{x^{ - 2}} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "problem": "\\int{{\\frac{7}{{3{y^6}}} + \\frac{1}{{{y^{10}}}} - \\frac{2}{{\\sqrt[3]{{{y^4}}}}}\\,dy}}",
            "answer": "{{ - \\frac{7}{{15}}{y^{ - 5}} - \\frac{1}{9}{y^{ - 9}} + 6{y^{ - \\,\\,\\frac{1}{3}}} + c}}"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "problem": "\\int{{\\sin \\left( x \\right) + 10{{\\csc }^2}\\left( x \\right)\\,dx}}",
            "answer": "{{ - \\cos \\left( x \\right) - 10\\cot \\left( x \\right) + c}}"
        }
    ]
}